import { LRQuestion } from './LRUtilities';

export type Challenge = {
  context: string;
  contextAudio?: string;
  task1: LRQuestion;
  task2: LRQuestion;
};

export const sampleChallenge: Challenge = {
  context: 'Here should be a context paragraph', // I added this and moved the audio file to contextAudio
  contextAudio: 'readingChallengeB2-1.mp3',
  task1: {
    // Here was a Question[] and the question is inside it but I changed it to LRQuestion immediately (need confirmation from Sayed)
    NumOfSubQuestions: 6,
    Question: 'Choose the correct answer, A, B or C.',
    QuestionType: 'Multiple Choice',
    SubQuestions: [
      {
        Choices: [
          "A- didn't start the company but manages it now.",
          'B- started the company and manages it now.',
          "C- tarted the company but doesn't manage it any more.",
        ],
        CorrectAnswer: 'B- started the company and manages it now.',
        QuestionText: ' Anna ... ',
      },
      {
        Choices: [
          'A- is for parents to learn from.',
          'B- is for students to learn from.',
          'C- is for students who want to find a tutor.',
        ],
        CorrectAnswer: 'C- is for students who want to find a tutor.',
        QuestionText: 'The app ...',
      },
      {
        Choices: [
          "A- don't have the time or knowledge to help with their children's homework.",
          "B- think that schools should help with their children's homework.",
          "C- don't want to help with their children's homework.",
        ],
        CorrectAnswer:
          "A- don't have the time or knowledge to help with their children's homework.",
        QuestionText: ' Many parents ... ',
      },
      {
        Choices: [
          'A- has student exercises on it.',
          'B- is only for people in remote areas.',
          'C-  offers live online support from tutors.',
        ],
        CorrectAnswer: 'C-  offers live online support from tutors.',
        QuestionText: 'The app ...',
      },
      {
        Choices: [
          'A- often charge lower rates.',
          'B-  often charge higher rates.',
          "C- don't like to work too much.",
        ],
        CorrectAnswer: 'A- often charge lower rates.',
        QuestionText: ' On the app, tutors who live in remote areas ... ',
      },
      {
        Choices: [
          'A- is new and not many people know about it.',
          'B- is already popular.',
          'C- is not very successful.',
        ],
        CorrectAnswer: 'B- is already popular.',
        QuestionText: 'The app ...',
      },
    ],
  },

  task2: {
    List: 'A a problem\nB a need\nC itself\nD the range of services\nE an idea\nF funding',
    ListTitle: 'List of nouns:',
    NumOfSubQuestions: 6,
    Question: 'Match the verbs and nouns from the interview.',
    QuestionType: 'List Selection',
    SubQuestions: [
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'A',
        QuestionText: 'to solve -answer-',
      },
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'E',
        QuestionText: ' to come up with -answer-',
      },
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'B',
        QuestionText: 'to meet -answer-',
      },
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'C',
        QuestionText: 'to speak for -answer-',
      },
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'F',
        QuestionText: 'to secure -answer-',
      },
      {
        Choices: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F'],
        CorrectAnswer: 'D',
        QuestionText: 'to expand -answer-',
      },
    ],
  },
};
